<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VOA on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/tags/voa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VOA on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 13:53:21 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/tags/voa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Voa Problems Happen When You Are &#39;Asleep at the Wheel&#39;</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/voa-problems-happen-when-you-are-asleep-at-the-wheel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 13:53:21 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/voa-problems-happen-when-you-are-asleep-at-the-wheel/</guid>
      
        <description>FILE - An man works his phone as he drives through traffic in Dallas, Tuesday, Feb. 26, 2013. Texas lawmakers are considering a statewide ban on texting while driving. (AP Photo/LM Otero) https://www.51voa.com/VOA_Special_English/problems-happen-when-you-are-asleep-at-the-wheel-89478.html Note Info (to fall or to be) + Asleep at the Wheel It means someone is not paying attention or is focused on what they are doing. This can cause all kinds of problems. We often use this expression to describe a person who is not thinking about possible future problems.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voa - Root of the Problem</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/voa-root-of-the-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 10:11:15 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/voa-root-of-the-problem/</guid>
      
        <description>In this Sept. 2, 2015 photo, ginseng grower Denny Colwell shows the rings that develop on older ginseng roots. (AP Photo/Keith Srakocic) https://www.51voa.com/VOA_Special_English/let-s-get-to-the-root-of-the-problem-88930.html Content Today we talk about we explore words and expression in the English language. To roots of most plants grow below the ground. There, they have some very inportant jobs. The roots anchor the plant. They secure it in the ground. Roots also take in water and minerals to feed the plant, the roots store food and nutrients.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VOA - Could Bitcoin Become a Reserve Currency</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/learn-en-voa-could-bitcoin-become-a-reserve-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 11:08:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/learn-en-voa-could-bitcoin-become-a-reserve-currency/</guid>
      
        <description>This is my series to learn english. I have a target 6.5 IELTS on next year. So, I&amp;rsquo;m looking for the most effective way to learn English. I will try my best to learn. I have to get it. These are the articles that I find interesting to read. I just pratice retyping the existing articles. Here is a root article: Could Bitcoin Become a Reserve Currency - by By Dan Novak 17 April 2022 Root Articles or you can find all at: https://www.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>