<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TTBaseUIKit on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/tags/ttbaseuikit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TTBaseUIKit on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:31:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/tags/ttbaseuikit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rebuiding train booking feature by SwiftUI in 12Bay application - Design</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-train-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:31:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-train-v2/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract Today, we are continuing our journey of learning SwiftUI by rebuilding the train booking feature in the 12Bay application. This function is designed to help users find trains that are available for their desired departure and arrival stations. Once users find their preferred train, the app will show them which seats are available for that specific journey. Users can then choose their preferred seat type, like window or aisle seats, and select the number of tickets they want to book.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12Bay integrated SwiftUI. With 12Bay, no StoryBoard, no XIB files, no cocoapods, ...</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-bus-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:37:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-bus-v2/</guid>
      
        <description>Bus booking function write by SwiftUI For three months, I dedicated myself to learning SwiftUI and using it to develop a bus booking feature. Along the way, I faced several challenges in integrating SwiftUI into an existing UIKit-based project. In my upcoming articles, I will dive deep into these challenges, providing detailed insights and solutions. But first, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the user interface for booking a ride, which includes selecting a bus route, choosing seats, and specifying pickup/drop-off points.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/ttbaseuikitswiftuiserial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:05:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/ttbaseuikitswiftuiserial/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract Info SwiftUI: It’s the future I realize that now is a suitable time to learn and apply SwiftUI in the real world. So in this series, I will delve into the fundamental components of SwiftUI. With the knowledge gained, we will update TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI, allowing us to quickly build applications using these basic components. Additionally, we will develop a new feature called &amp;lsquo;Bus Booking&amp;rsquo; using SwiftUI on the 12Bay application.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to design the food selection in a mobile application</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/devlife-12bay-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 14:00:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/devlife-12bay-food/</guid>
      
        <description>Long time no see! Just keep doing it and you&amp;rsquo;ll reach your goals.
Abstract So, today we will be discussing about how to design the food selection in a mobile application. In this post, we will explore
Improve your mindset about developing applications. Working on Swift, Sketch. Let&amp;rsquo;s do it.
What is the purpose of the function? The main purpose is to provide more utility to customers using the 12bay application.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Update Current Cocoapod Lib to Support SwiftPM</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/how-to-update-cocoapod-lib-to-support-swiftpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 11:10:07 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/how-to-update-cocoapod-lib-to-support-swiftpm/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract Today we will discuss how to update the cocoapod library to support SwiftPM. Last week, I updated my TTBaseUIkit library to support Swift Package Manager. So I want to share some useful experience with you.
What is Swift Package Manager? First, if you don&amp;rsquo;t know about Swift Package Manager. I thought you read swiftpm-post to understand about this package.
The Swift Package Manager is a tool for managing the distribution of Swift code.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swift Package Manager (SwiftPM) vs Cocoapods</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/cocoapods-with-swiftpm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2022 16:21:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/cocoapods-with-swiftpm/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract Today we will talk about dependency managers in iOS and compare their advantages and disadvantages. Finally, we learn how to use those to add dependencies to your project.
Dependencies When we build applications, we often use code from other developers writing to build more powerful applications more quickly. In your projects, we can make an easy animation to hide or show the button. But if you want to add a complex animation to your project that’s not built-in.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTBaseUIKit - Framework to build UI programmatically</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/ttbaseuikit-ui-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 16:50:03 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/ttbaseuikit-ui-framework/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract When I work with many projects. I always ask myself how to optimize the application, reusable code and how to develop the fastest and most efficient applications. So after two years of working with Swift language. I created the framework to build UI programmatically. With TTBaseUIKit, you can build apps in the fastest and most efficient way. A few points to note when you apply this framework:
How to set up the framework Basic config settings Usage example Introduction I have been building framework for 5 years and for now, I still update new functions.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>