<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SwiftUI Serial - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/series/swiftui-serial-updating-ttbaseuikit-to-support-swiftui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SwiftUI Serial - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:31:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/series/swiftui-serial-updating-ttbaseuikit-to-support-swiftui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rebuiding train booking feature by SwiftUI in 12Bay application - Design</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-train-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:31:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-train-v2/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract Today, we are continuing our journey of learning SwiftUI by rebuilding the train booking feature in the 12Bay application. This function is designed to help users find trains that are available for their desired departure and arrival stations. Once users find their preferred train, the app will show them which seats are available for that specific journey. Users can then choose their preferred seat type, like window or aisle seats, and select the number of tickets they want to book.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the Spacer and how do we use it in SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/swiftui-spacer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 16:05:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/swiftui-spacer/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract In this article, we will learn about Spacer in SwiftUI. We will dive into the world of Spacer. Exploring their purpose, functionality and practical applications. This article is part of the SwiftUI Series - SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI
What is the Spacer? The Spacer is a layout view that expands to fill available space within a container.
Here is the definition from Apple. You can view full details at developer.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12Bay integrated SwiftUI. With 12Bay, no StoryBoard, no XIB files, no cocoapods, ...</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-bus-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:37:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-bus-v2/</guid>
      
        <description>Bus booking function write by SwiftUI For three months, I dedicated myself to learning SwiftUI and using it to develop a bus booking feature. Along the way, I faced several challenges in integrating SwiftUI into an existing UIKit-based project. In my upcoming articles, I will dive deep into these challenges, providing detailed insights and solutions. But first, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the user interface for booking a ride, which includes selecting a bus route, choosing seats, and specifying pickup/drop-off points.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand View in SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/uiview-vs-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:40:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/uiview-vs-view/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract In this article, we will learn about view in SwiftUI. This article is part of the SwiftUI Series - SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI
View is a function of state, not a sequence of events - apple
Woaaaa !
SwiftUI - Apple&amp;rsquo;s declarative framework for building user interfaces. The user interface is defined based on the current state of the application, and any changes to the state automatically update the corresponding views.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand safe area in SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/understand-safearea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:21:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/understand-safearea/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract In this article, we will learn about Safe Area in SwiftUI. This article is part of the SwiftUI Series - SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI
Related knowledge What is the Layout? In the Apple ecosystem, Layout refers to the process of arranging and positioning user interface elements such as views and controls on a screen or within a container view using layout constraints, Auto Layout, or SwiftUI.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WWDC23 from the perspective of an iOS developer</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/wwdc23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 15:42:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/wwdc23/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract WWDC23 - Code new worlds - Since the event took place, I have been following updates on SwiftUI. It demonstrates the importance of SwiftUI in Apple&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem. And more than just a new product, Vision Pro shows a direction for the future, which could change the way we interact, communicate, and work. It takes time for this product to prove itself - a revolutionary product like the iPhone or not?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/ttbaseuikitswiftuiserial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 16:05:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/ttbaseuikitswiftuiserial/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract Info SwiftUI: It’s the future I realize that now is a suitable time to learn and apply SwiftUI in the real world. So in this series, I will delve into the fundamental components of SwiftUI. With the knowledge gained, we will update TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI, allowing us to quickly build applications using these basic components. Additionally, we will develop a new feature called &amp;lsquo;Bus Booking&amp;rsquo; using SwiftUI on the 12Bay application.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>