<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>VNUHCM on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/categories/vnuhcm/</link>
    <description>Recent content in VNUHCM on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:04:17 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/categories/vnuhcm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Predictive modelling of diseases based on a network and machine learning approach (book of abstracts - my paper)</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/my-paper-disease-prediction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 16:04:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/my-paper-disease-prediction/</guid>
      
        <description>End of year 2022. I just got a paper at the ACIIDS 2022 conference. So I want to share with you about this. I hope that it is a motivation to make the new goals for the next year.
 BOOK OF ABSTRACTS Abstract Chronic diseases have become the first prioritized concern of the health industry, so understanding the disease progression is necessary for predicting, planning and preparing resources to prevent and cure the diseases most effectively.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latex Take Notes</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/latex-take-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 14:29:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/latex-take-note/</guid>
      
        <description>The 14th Asian Conference on Intelligent Information and Database Systems
https://aciids.pwr.edu.pl/2022/download/ACIIDS_2022_HCMC_Flyer_v.7.0.pdf
 MY TOPIC: Predictive modelling of diseases based on a network and machine learning approach, I hope it&amp;rsquo;s approved soon ^^
 Paper Submission:
The proceedings of ACIIDS 2022 will be published by Springer in series Lecture Notes in Artificial Intelligence and will be distributed at the conference
 LNCS/LNAI style. Should not exceed 13 pages.   Here is a my collect data with purpose to learn, more knowledge from large amount of examples, solutions, and ideas on the internet.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Factorization Machines &amp; their application on huge datasets Presentation</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 15:45:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines-presentation/</guid>
      
        <description>Báo cáo này dựa trên bài báo Introductory Guide – Factorization Machines &amp;amp; their application on huge datasets (with codes in Python)  Tác giả: Ankit Choudhary
 Một số từ khóa liên quan
FMs: Factorization Machines, FFMs: Field Aware Factorization Machines, Matrix Factorization CTR: Click-Through Rate, Recommendation Systems
Slide share  </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FACTORIZATION MACHINES AND THEIR APPLICATION ON HUGE DATASETS</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 13:29:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines/</guid>
      
        <description>Giới thiệu tổng quát về Factorization Machines và ứng dụng của nó trên tập dữ liệu lớn Dựa trên bài báo Introductory Guide – Factorization Machines &amp;amp; their application on huge datasets (with codes in Python), tác giả: Ankit Choudhary
 Phần mở đầu Khi chúng ta làm việc với các bài toán liên quan tới Click Prediction Problem hay Recommendation Systems. Chúng ta thường xuyên đối mặt với vấn đề là tập dữ liệu quá lớn.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>