<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Notes on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/categories/notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Notes on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:37:02 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/categories/notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>12Bay integrated SwiftUI. With 12Bay, no StoryBoard, no XIB files, no cocoapods, ...</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-bus-v2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 15:37:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/12bay-bus-v2/</guid>
      
        <description>Bus booking function write by SwiftUI For three months, I dedicated myself to learning SwiftUI and using it to develop a bus booking feature. Along the way, I faced several challenges in integrating SwiftUI into an existing UIKit-based project. In my upcoming articles, I will dive deep into these challenges, providing detailed insights and solutions. But first, let&amp;rsquo;s explore the user interface for booking a ride, which includes selecting a bus route, choosing seats, and specifying pickup/drop-off points.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand View in SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/uiview-vs-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 11:40:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/uiview-vs-view/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract In this article, we will learn about view in SwiftUI. This article is part of the SwiftUI Series - SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI
 View is a function of state, not a sequence of events - apple
  Woaaaa !
 SwiftUI - Apple&amp;rsquo;s declarative framework for building user interfaces. The user interface is defined based on the current state of the application, and any changes to the state automatically update the corresponding views.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understand safe area in SwiftUI</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/understand-safearea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:21:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/job/ios/swiftui/understand-safearea/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract In this article, we will learn about Safe Area in SwiftUI. This article is part of the SwiftUI Series - SwiftUI Series - Updating TTBaseUIKit to support SwiftUI
 Related knowledge What is the Layout? In the Apple ecosystem, Layout refers to the process of arranging and positioning user interface elements such as views and controls on a screen or within a container view using layout constraints, Auto Layout, or SwiftUI.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common phrases in English</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/note/commonphrases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 16:10:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/note/commonphrases/</guid>
      
        <description>These are the phrase notes I record to remember what I learn while studying English. You can easily search for specific words or descriptions to find what you need quickly.&amp;quot;
 Type something in the input field to search the table for keywords or description:
   $(document).ready(function(){ $(&#34;#myInput&#34;).on(&#34;keyup&#34;, function() { var value = $(this).val().toLowerCase(); $(&#34;table tbody tr&#34;).filter(function() { $(this).toggle($(this).text().toLowerCase().indexOf(value)  -1) }); }); });      Phrases Define More     No wonder (I am) not surprised at all (that).</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s the difference between who, whom, and whose, and how do we use these?</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/learnenglish/grammar/who-whom-whose/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 13:54:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/learnenglish/grammar/who-whom-whose/</guid>
      
        <description>When I was learning english, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to distinguish between who, whom and whose. So this post i am noting some keywords to remember. Some knowledge has been extracted from www.myenglishpages.com.&amp;quot;
 The main point &amp;ldquo;Who,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;whom,&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;whose&amp;rdquo; are all relative pronouns used in English to refer to  people, animals, or things previously mentioned in a sentence.
Info Who is used as the subject of a sentence or clause (refers to the person who is doing the action).</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Notes in Economics</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/note/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 14:42:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/note/economics/</guid>
      
        <description>These are the small notes that I record to remember while reading books about economics or learning about financial knowledge. With so many terms and concepts that I don&amp;rsquo;t understand, I make a point to write them down to aid my studies. You can easily search for specific words or descriptions to find what you need quickly.
 Type something in the input field to search the table for keywords or description:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latex Take Notes</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/latex-take-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 14:29:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/latex-take-note/</guid>
      
        <description>The 14th Asian Conference on Intelligent Information and Database Systems
https://aciids.pwr.edu.pl/2022/download/ACIIDS_2022_HCMC_Flyer_v.7.0.pdf
 MY TOPIC: Predictive modelling of diseases based on a network and machine learning approach, I hope it&amp;rsquo;s approved soon ^^
 Paper Submission:
The proceedings of ACIIDS 2022 will be published by Springer in series Lecture Notes in Artificial Intelligence and will be distributed at the conference
 LNCS/LNAI style. Should not exceed 13 pages.   Here is a my collect data with purpose to learn, more knowledge from large amount of examples, solutions, and ideas on the internet.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The vision</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/note/cryptocurrency_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 08:21:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/note/cryptocurrency_world/</guid>
      
        <description>Cryptocurrency World
Type something in the input field to search the table for keywords or description:
   $(document).ready(function(){ $(&#34;#myInput&#34;).on(&#34;keyup&#34;, function() { var value = $(this).val().toLowerCase(); $(&#34;table tbody tr&#34;).filter(function() { $(this).toggle($(this).text().toLowerCase().indexOf(value)  -1) }); }); });       Key Define More     **ví metamask S&amp;amp;P 500 is a stock market index in the United States that includes 500 of the largest and most popular companies.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>