<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 15:45:29 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Factorization Machines &amp; their application on huge datasets Presentation</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 15:45:29 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Báo cáo này dựa trên bài báo Introductory Guide – Factorization Machines &amp;amp; their application on huge datasets (with codes in Python)  Tác giả: Ankit Choudhary
 Một số từ khóa liên quan
FMs: Factorization Machines, FFMs: Field Aware Factorization Machines, Matrix Factorization CTR: Click-Through Rate, Recommendation Systems
Slide share  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FACTORIZATION MACHINES AND THEIR APPLICATION ON HUGE DATASETS</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 13:29:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/factorization-machines/</guid>
      <description>Giới thiệu tổng quát về Factorization Machines và ứng dụng của nó trên tập dữ liệu lớn Dựa trên bài báo Introductory Guide – Factorization Machines &amp;amp; their application on huge datasets (with codes in Python), tác giả: Ankit Choudhary
 Phần mở đầu Khi chúng ta làm việc với các bài toán liên quan tới Click Prediction Problem hay Recommendation Systems. Chúng ta thường xuyên đối mặt với vấn đề là tập dữ liệu quá lớn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is the Future of Mobile App Development</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/what-is-the-future-of-mobile-app-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 16:05:26 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/what-is-the-future-of-mobile-app-development/</guid>
      <description>💡 What is the future of mobile app development?  A new year has started and most of us are probably figuring out what we should focus on this year. Whether it’s learning new things or expanding our knowledge on topics we’ve already learned about in the past, there’s always something that deserves our attention in the world of iOS development.
 As per the statistics, over 5 million apps are available in Google Play Store and Apple App Store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Ci Cd Gitlab Fastlane</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/basic-ci-cd-gitlab-fastlane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2021 10:38:57 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/basic-ci-cd-gitlab-fastlane/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Trong bài viết này mình tiềm hiểu về GitLab-CI, Fastlane ở mức cơ bản.
   Tìm hiểu GitLab-CI.
  Fastlane là gì?
   What is CI? Trong quá trình làm việc theo nhóm việc quản lý source-code giữa các thành viên với nhau là cực kỳ quan trọng. Việc cập nhật mã code giữa các thành viên với nhau là rất thường xuyên. Việc này dẫn đến nhiều vấn đề nảy sinh như code lỗi,&amp;hellip; để phát hiện sớm các lỗi để sửa ngay đưa ra một khái niệm là Continuos Integration - Tích hợp liên tục</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing On Ios Application Implement Viper Clean Architecture In An Ios App</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/nlp-on-ios-application-viper-arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 13:11:55 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/nlp-on-ios-application-viper-arch/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Xây dựng ứng dụng iOS với kiến trúc VIPER về dự đoán tác giả bài thơ. Input đầu vào là một đoạn text đoạn thơ người dùng nhập vào và output là tác giả của đoạn thơ đó. Ví dụ: INPUT = Sao anh không về chơi thôn Vĩ? → OUTPUT = Hàn Mặc Tử
  Tìm hiểu về Bag of Words, Turi Create. Xây dựng ứng dụng iOS trên kiến trúc VIPER Clean Architecture Một số từ khóa liên quan: Bag of Word, Logictic Classifier, Turi Create VIPER, iOS Application     Đặt Vấn Đề INPUT STRING:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The VIPER Architecture</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 15:58:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Architecture Just like MVC or MVVM, VIPER is a design pattern created to facilitate the development by creating layers of abstraction and isolation of concerns, creating a cleaner code, and bringing more maintainability further down the road
VIPER is an acronym for View-Interactor-Presenter-Entity-Router. Each functionality or module must be defined by these five components.
View It’s what the user sees, the view that represents a functionality. In some cases, a single functionality can have multiple views, for example, an onboarding flow with multiple steps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
