<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UI-programmatically on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/tags/ui-programmatically/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UI-programmatically on Tuan Truong&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 14:00:33 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tqtuan1201.github.io/tags/ui-programmatically/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to design the food selection in a mobile application</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/devlife-12bay-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 14:00:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/devlife-12bay-food/</guid>
      
        <description>Long time no see! Just keep doing it and you&amp;rsquo;ll reach your goals.
 Abstract So, today we will be discussing about how to design the food selection in a mobile application. In this post, we will explore
 Improve your mindset about developing applications. Working on Swift, Sketch.  Let&amp;rsquo;s do it.
 What is the purpose of the function? The main purpose is to provide more utility to customers using the 12bay application.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTBaseUIKit - Framework to build UI programmatically</title>
      <link>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/ttbaseuikit-ui-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 16:50:03 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tqtuan1201.github.io/posts/ttbaseuikit-ui-framework/</guid>
      
        <description>Abstract When I work with many projects. I always ask myself how to optimize the application, reusable code and how to develop the fastest and most efficient applications. So after two years of working with Swift language. I created the framework to build UI programmatically. With TTBaseUIKit, you can build apps in the fastest and most efficient way. A few points to note when you apply this framework:
 How to set up the framework Basic config settings Usage example  Introduction I have been building framework for 5 years and for now, I still update new functions.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>